Hello, today helmets were distributed among the children in A.B. Niketan School in Khagol. Let us
tell you that hundreds of helmets were distributed among the children by Patna Traffic Police and ICICI
Lord
and the children were instructed
that if they come to school on a bike with their father, they have to
wear a helmet
or if they go anywhere, they have to wear a helmet.
Let us tell you what you are saying to the
traffic police officer who
distributed these. A big
plea to you,
come here. Thank
you, thank you, we will
wear this helmet whenever we will right. So, thank you so much sir. Thank you so much sir. We will also
suggest others to wear this helmet and
whenever we ride a bike,
this helmet will remain with us. This is a call
once again from you.
In the near future, 18000
helmets are to be distributed. It is often
seen that parents drive
but their children do not  Children do not
wear helmets and many times it has been seen that
due to wearing helmet or not wearing helmet,
in both the situations those who
wear helmet remain safe but those who do
not wear helmet
often die in accidents, that is why
this is a small beginning by the traffic police,
a small beginning,
in the recent times the
highway patrol has been formed by the government,
now everything is going to be an automatic system in the highway patrolling vehicle
and under this,
in the first phase,
23 vehicles of highway patrol vehicle have been put
on the roads by the government and there will be
automatic challan in it, if children are not
wearing helmets or even adults are not wearing helmets then they will have to be
fined, now our
initiative of traffic police is going to be
based on technology and this is
a small beginning to stop the increasing number of death rate of our children,
this effort of ours will continue in future also,
your cooperation
is required, I will always continue this program,
Dhan Apnay ji, I am
Pawan Raman Prakash B from Traffic Division Bihar Patna.  Get
your home walls decorated with Polygar Knight and
contact RK Superstar.